BAYAN HAMMADEH

Back End Developer

Back-end developer with 5+ years of back-end development. Build web applications, which are fit for purpose, functionally correct and meets the user's precise needs. I have a record of accomplishment of using new technologies to bring software products to life. On a personal level, I am full of energy and passion. Right now, I would like to join a company where there is a culture of encouragement, respect and teamwork.

Contact Information

Phone

+963940212527

Email

bayanahammadeh@gmail.com

Github

- https://github.com/bayanahammadeh
 LinkedIn
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/bayan-hammadeh-7b9113220

Education

DAMASCUS UNIVERSITY

Information Technology Engineering

Skills

PHP, Laravel, JavaScript, MySQL, HTML, Bootstrap, CSS, Linux, Basics of CEH.

Work Experiences

NANS -- DAMASCUS, SYRIA, 2016 to Present

FULL STACK Developer

- Experience in front-end development, code the front-end of a website, bring the web designer's design to life, and ensure responsive design.
- Experience in back-end development, work behind the scene, building and maintain the technology needed to power the front-end, ensure that everything the front-end developer builds is fully functional.
- Create and manage the database.

VULNERABILITY SCANNING TOOLS

Experience in using Vulnerability scanning tools like, Yaazhini, Ostorlab, Wireshark, Acunetix, Burp suite

LINUX

Ability writing Linux script.

AGRICULTURE MINISTRY -- DAMASCUS, SYRIA, 2007 to 2015

DESKTOP APPLICATION PRGRAMMING

Programming several desktop programs.

CIDAR COMPANY -- DAMASCUS, SYRIA, 2006 to 2007

DESKTOP APPLICATION PRGRAMMING

 Programming desktop program to manage all accounting operations and warehouse management.

Completed projects

TOOLS

https://tools.ecc.sy/

Tools is a web application that offers many services such as generate certificate signing requests (CSRs), generate public/private keys, view "digital certificate or csr" properties, in addition to many other features. User-friendly interface, advanced features.

Developed with Laravel, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and JavaScript.

CV

https://github.com/bayanahammadeh/cv

CV is a Bayan Hammmadeh Portfolio
Developed with Laravel, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and JavaScript.

Dashboard

https://github.com/bayanahammadeh/Dashboard
 Dashboard is a Dashboard for Bayan Hammmadeh Portfolio
 Developed with Laravel, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and JavaScript.

Courses and Qualifications

NANS -- Damascus, Syria --2018

Basics of Network

NANS -- Damascus, Syria --2018

Basics of Linux

NANS -- Damascus, Syria --2018

Advance of Linux

MOSCOW, RUSSIA --2019

Public key infrastructure

SSS -- Damascus, Syria --2020

Basics of CEH

SSS -- Damascus, Syria --2020

Basics of PYTHON

Languages

Arabic

English